为什么一个天使要救我出地狱呢
And why would an angel rescue me from hell
因为我们有任务交给你
Because we have work for you.
你要学的东西还多着呢  兔崽子
You got a lot to learn,boy.
那是真的吗  是我打破了第一道封印吗
Is it true? Did I break the first seal?
一切都是我造成的对吗  是的
Did I start all this? Yes.
为什么你们不干脆把我留在那里
Why didn't you just leave me there,then?
开启这一切的正义之人
The righteous man who begins it
就是唯一能终结这一切的人
Is the only one who can finish it.
你必须阻止这一切
You have to stop it.
我们的命运由你决定
Our fate rests with you.
去找别人吧
Find someone else.
我不是你说的那个人
It's not me.
'Cause he gets up in the morning
And he goes to work at 9
And he comes back home at 5:30
Gets the same train every time
'Cause his world is built 'round punctuality
It never fails
And he's oh so good
And he's oh
公共关系早间咨询
PR morning edition.
本周正是...
It's time for this week...
He's a well-respected man about town
Doing the best things so conservatively
And he likes his own backyard
And he likes his fags the best
'Cause he's better than the rest
And his own sweat smells the best
And he hopes to grab his father's loot
迪恩·斯密斯
市场营销部经理
When pater passes on
'Cause he's oh so good
And he's...
我想知道的就是
All I want to know is,
他们什么时候才会有另一个像"天桥骄子"这样的真人秀节目
When are they gonna have another show like "Project Runway"?
...And his mind
He's a well-respected man about town
Doing the best things so...
暂时不说网络收益的问题
Net profitability aside,
我关心的是客户数量的增长率
It's the client-retention rate that concerns me,
面对面销售利润的最大值
Vis-a-Vis maximizing return on sales.
看过数据表之后给我打电话
Buzz me back once you've seen the spreadsheets.
-艾德勒先生  -迪恩
- Mr. Adler. - Dean.
-干得好  -干得好
- Good stuff. - Good stuff?
大赚一票哦
Big things.
-干得好  -干得好
- Good stuff. -Good stuff.
我听到你说的了  我很久没去健身房了
Oh,I hear you. I haven't been to the gym in ages.
我自己有点得意扬扬
Carrying a little bloat around myself.
是的  这是一成不变的生活作风  我的朋友  独一无二
Yeah,it's a sedentary lifestyle,my man. No two ways.
好吧  再给我说一次
All right, tell me one more time.
你是说  嗯  柠檬和...和什么？
You said,uh,lemon and -- what was it?
辣椒和枫树糖浆
Cayenne and maple syrup.
你不是开玩笑吧
Are you serious?
你损失了多少钱
How much did you lose?
He's a well-respected man about town
Doing the best things so conservatively
我们认识吗
Do I know you?
应该不认识
I don't think so.
很抱歉  哥们儿  你看着真眼熟
I'm sorry,man. You just look really familiar.
这话留着去健身室说去吧  你个小同
Save it for the health club, pal.
[邪恶力量 第4季第17集]
技术支持部  这是萨姆·威森
Tech support. This is Sam Wesson.
好吧  你试着关机之后再开机了吗
Okay. Uh,well,did you try turning it off and then on?
好吧  直接关机
Okay,go ahead and turn it off.
不  不...  就...就直接关机
No,no,no,no. just -- just off.
好了  现在等一下
All right,give it a second.
开机
Turn it back on.
好吧  它是...是不是开始打印了
Okay,is it -- is it printing now?
很好
Great.
随时欢迎
Anytime.
你觉得小秘怎么样
What do you think of,uh,Mimi?
她还不错
She's okay.
也许有机会搞上她
Might have to hit that.
哥们儿  你们年纪也差太多了
Oh,dude,that's totally age-inappropriate.
经验
Experience.
老花镜
Uh,trifocals.
她可是御姐来着  萨姆  我知道的
There's a milf there,Sam. I just know it.
也许是御奶奶
Maybe a gmilf.
来吧
Come on.
咖啡小憩
Coffee break?
那是当然
Yeah,for sure.
保罗  是时候补充能量了  哥们儿
Paul, time for a refuel,buddy.
对不起  没时间
Sorry. No time.
什么时候开始的
Since when?
哥们儿  我们是算时薪的
Dude,we get paid by the hour.
我在工作
Working!
好吧
Okay.
他看起来压力挺大的
He seems stressed.
也许只是有点反常
Probably just freaked.
因为他上网浏览色情图片被降职了
'cause he got busted surfing porn on the internet.
不  不  不  等一下  什么时候
No,no,no. Wait. When?
他昨天被人力资源叫走的
He got sent up to h.r. yesterday.
估计他们把他吓破胆了
Guess they put the fear of god in him.
伊恩  哥们儿
Ian! Dude!
就是购购物  家里的刚用完
Just doing a little shopping. Running low at home.
那么  萨姆...
So,Sam...
你最近还做那些梦吗
Had any of those dreams lately?
怎么了  别那样
What? Don't be like that.
来吧  这是我一天最期待的时刻
Come on. It's the highlight of my day.
我一开始就不该告诉你
I never should have told you in the first place.
你的梦棒极了
They're genius!
说吧  哥们儿  和同学们一起分享下
Don't hold out on me,dude. Share with the class.
你肯定会嘲笑我的
You're just gonna be a dick about it.
什么？！ 绝对不会
What?! No way!
我绝对不会嘲笑你的  放心
I won't say a word -- total respect.
说吧
Go.
我梦见我从恶魔手里救了一个叫泰莎的死神
I dreamt that I saved a grim reaper named Tessa from demons.
太经典了
Classic!
你小时候玩过多少次龙与地下城
How much d&d did youou play when you were a kid?
哦  天哪
Oh,my.
好吧  你救了一个死神
Okay,so you're rescuing the grim reaper.
你是个大英雄
You're a hero.
谢天谢地我们这里也有哈利波特了
I mean,thank god we got Harry Potter here.
拯救我们远离天启
To save us all from the apocalypse.
混蛋
Dick.
巫师
Wizard.
萨姆·维森
Sam Wesson
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
哥们儿  我可不是个基佬
Look,man,I told you, I'm not into the --
拜托  我也不是
Oh,dude,come on. I'm not either.
我只是想问你个问题
I just want to ask you one question.
好吧
Sure.
你觉得世界上有鬼吗
What do you think about ghosts?
鬼
Ghosts?
你相信有鬼吗
Do you believe in them?
说实话  我还真没怎么想过
Uh,tell you the truth,I've never given it much thought.
那吸血鬼呢
Vampires?
什么
What?
为什么问这个
Why?
因为我最近做了一些很奇怪的梦
'cause i've been having some...weird dreams lately.
明白我的意思吗
You know what I mean?
不太明白
No,not really.
你从来没有做过奇怪的梦吗
So... You've never had any...weird dreams?
听着  伙计
All right,look,man, uh...
我不认识你  好吗
I don't know you,okay?
但是我要告诉你些事
But I'm gonna do a public service
你话太多了
And,uh,let you know that -- that you over-share.
你试过关上开关再打开吗
Did you turn it off,then on?
好吧  试试看
All right, well,let's try that.
不  没事  我等着
No,no,it's fine. i'll wait.
吸血鬼
在打印了吗
Is it printing now?
很好
Oh,that's great.
随时为您效劳
Anytime.
在干嘛呢
Whatcha doin'?
没什么
Nothing.
人力资源部给你发电邮了吗
You get an e-mail from human resources?
没有啊  为什么这么问
No. why?
靠  难道只有我收到
Damn it. guess it's just me,then.
他们让我  到人力资源部报道
I'm supposed to,quote, "report to H.R.," unquote.
没准他们发现你
Well,they're probably finally busting you
把办公用品都偷光了
For snaking all those office supplies.
希望只是打屁股而已
I hope they spank me.
不  不  不
No,no,no,no,no,no.
拜托
Come on!
别这样对我啊
Don't do this to me. please!
哥们  你没事吧
Hey,man. you okay?
死机了
It froze.
保罗  这种垃圾配置  死机很正常
They're crap,Paul. they freeze all the time.
你不明白
You don't understand. when -- when
我重启了
I rebooted, ever
但是一整天的心血都白费了
A whole day's work -- deleted.
你备份了吗
Well,did you back up?
不  没有
No,i didn't back up.
多希望我备份了  但是我没有
I wish to god I backed up, but I didn't.
我要找回来  我会找到的
I'll get it back. I'll find it.
一定就在什么地方
It's somewhere.
一定要找到
Find it!
保罗  没事的  这很正常
Paul,it's okay,man. these things happen.
不要啊
Come on!
拜托  拜托
Please! please!
所有文件都  不见了
All that work... Gone.
完了
Failed.
不要加热鱼  很臭  谢谢合作
有些事好像不太对劲
Something seem not right ?
是啊  整件事都不对劲
Uh,yeah. Try the whole thing.
告诉你  伙计
I'm telling you,man...
我再也不会吃爆米花了
I'll never eat popcorn again.
没错
Yeah,right.
桑多弗公司个人档案
员工姓名  保罗·邓巴
特别提示时间   09年4月14日  2周后
请公司职员参加退休聚会  要通知所有的高级职员和主管经理
还有两周
Two weeks?
为什么会有人
Hey,why would someone kill themselves
在退休前两周自杀呢
Two weeks before they were supposed to retire?
我是说  保罗再过两周就自由了
I mean,Paul was two weeks from freedom.
他应该很开心才对  是不
He should have been... happy,right?
我没时间说这个  萨姆
I don't have time for this,Sam.
你真搞笑
That's very funny.
你怎么了
What's with you?
我在工作  很重要的
I'm working. it's important.
人力资源部教训你了还是怎么
H.r. bust your balls or something?
你穿着工作服
You're wearing the shirt.
你刮胡子了吗
Did you shave?
技术支持部  我是伊恩
Tech support. this is Ian.
马上就来
Be right up.
我得去22楼  找主管谈谈
I have to go up to 22, speak to a manager.
伊恩  对吧
Hi. "Ian," is it?
好  进来吧
Mm-hmm. yeah,come on in.
昨天你填写了445号工作表
Yesterday, you filled out a 445-t.
没有大问题  但有几处小错
And,uh,no problem -- just a -- just a few errors.
我是说  我们刚换成Vista系统
I mean,we did just switch over to vista,so i'm sure
我想你习惯于填写只读光盘表吧  对不
You're used to filling out the dash-r's,am i right?
不
Oh,no.
不  没关系  没关系
No,no,no. it's fine. it's fine.
我只是想要你今天重新做一份
I just need you to redo one today
等我开完发票就可以了
So i can get the show on the road with the invoicing.
我的天啊
Oh,my god.
没事的  就是重做一份  时间很充足
No,it's fine. just re-file it, and we're square.
真不敢相信我居然做错了
I can't believe i did this. i can't --
真不敢相信  真不敢相信我居然做错了
I can't believe it. i...can't believe i did this.
哥们  别这样
Hey,guy,come on --
不  不
No,no.
它影响利润了  我搞砸了
It affected profits. it -- i screwed up.
我  我不敢相信  不敢相信
I-I can't -- I can't --
非常抱歉
I am so sorry.
我怎么能这么做
How could i do that?
我对不起桑多弗
I failed Sandover.
我对不起公司
I failed the company.
伊恩 你先坐下
Uh,why don't you sit down,Ian?
不
No.
伊恩  伊恩
Ian. Ian!
伊恩
Ian,hey.
冷静下  伙计  好吗
Just chill out,man. okay?
我们还是出去吧
H-hey,maybe we should get out of here,huh?
走吧
Come on.
伊恩
Ian.
看着我
Look at me.
来人帮帮忙
Somebody help me!
我  我跟着他进了洗手间
I,uh,i-i followed him into the bathroom.
他就
He was,uh...
他就站在镜子前面
He was standing there in front of the mirror,
然后就
And then --
他把铅笔刺进了自己的脖子
...and,uh,he stabbed himself in the neck.
抱歉 这
I'm sorry. that's,uh...
技术支持部， 你好 我是萨姆
Tech support. this is sam.
马上来我办公室
I need to see you in my office -- now.
快进来 把门关上
Come on in. shut the door.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
我自己也不知道
I'm not sure i know.
你什么意思
What the hell does that mean?
我叫萨姆韦森  我三星期前才来上班
Sam wesson. i started here three weeks ago.
好吧
All right.
你在电梯里把我叫住
You cornered me in the elevator,
谈论鬼魂
Talking about ghosts.
而现在
And now...
现在怎样
Now what?
没什么
Now nothing.
我
I,uh...
你是三星期前来的公司  对吧
So,you started working here three weeks ago,huh?
我也是
Me too.
这个是超纯水
It's,uh, master cleanse.
你喝过吗
You tried it?
看样子大家都不喜欢做健康疗程
Phenomenal. detoxes you like nobody's business.
当你和伊恩在洗手间的时候
When you were in that bathroom with ian...
你有看到什么吗
Did you see something?
我知道我看到的是什么东西
I don't know. i don't know what i saw.
等等  你是说你
Wait. are you saying that --
你看见鬼魂了
Did you...see a ghost?
我当时吓傻了
I was freaking out.
那人把铅笔插进自己的脖子
The guy penciled his damn neck.
你有看到  对吧
You did,didn't you?
好吧  听着
Okay,listen --
会不会这些自杀其实并不是自杀
What if these suicides... aren't suicides?
我是说  如果有些什么东西
I mean, w-what if there's something...
非自然的
Not natural?
难道真的有鬼魂
So,what -- ghosts are real?
而且它们要对这些命案负责
And they're responsible for all the dead bodies around here?
你是想说这些
Is that what you're telling me?
听着
Look...
我知道这有点疯狂
I know it sounds crazy.
不过  的确就是我想说的
But yes -- that's what i'm telling you.
你的根据是什么
Uh-huh. based on what?
直觉
Instinct?
我也这么觉得
I've got the same instinct.
真的吗
Seriously?
还记得我跟你说的那些梦吗
You know those dreams i was telling you about?
我梦到了鬼魂
I was dreaming about ghosts.
-是吗  -这些鬼魂出现在现实生活中了
-Yeah? -And then it turns out that there's a real ghost.
你是想说你的梦能预见未来
So you're telling me that your dreams are special visions
跟那种通灵的人一样
And you're some kind of psychic?
当然不是  那太神经了
No. i mean that would be nuts.
我只是说
I-i'm just saying,
这里确实发生了一些怪事  对吧
Something weird is definitely going on around here,right?
所以我做了些调查
So i've been digging around a little.
我想我找到了这两个人的联系
I think i found a connection between the two guys.
你盗了他们的邮箱帐号
You broke into their e-mail accounts?
我只是用了些非常手段
I used...some skills that i happen to have
来满足我的好奇心
To... satisfy my curiosity.
不错
Nice.
好吧
Yeah,okay.
伊恩和保罗都曾收到相同的电子邮件
So,it turns out ian and paul both got this same e-mail
要他们到1444房间的人力资源部报到
Telling them to report to h.r.,room 1444.
人力资源部在7楼
HR's on 7.
问题就在这里
Exactly.
我们要不要去查一下
Should we go check this out?
现在吗
Like...right now?
不  有点太晚了  你是对的
No. no,it's getting late. you're right.
我现在就想去一探究竟
I am dying to check this out right now.
是吗
Right?
有人吗
Hello?
哇哦
Whoa.
你怎么知道该那么做
How'd you know how to do that?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
刚才真险 老兄
Holy crap,dude.
是啊
Yeah.
我想喝点啤酒
I could use a beer.
不好意思  我在做健康疗程
Oh,sorry,man. i'm on the cleanse.
我把所有不健康的东西都扔了
I got rid of all the carbs in the house.
你是怎么知道
Hey,how the hell did you know
那些鬼魂害怕扳手
That ghosts are scared of wrenches?
很疯狂 不是吗
Crazy,right?
你踢的那一脚也不错
And nice job kicking in that door,too.
很像李连杰
That was very jet li.
你是黑带还是什么级别的
What are you -- like, a black belt or something?
不
No.
我根本不知道我干嘛要那样
I have no clue how i did that.
好像我们之前就干过这个
It's like... we've done this before.
你说之前是什么意思
What do you mean, "before"?
就像莎莉·麦克琳的之前
Like "shirley maclaine" before?
不是
No.
我很难摆脱这种感觉
I just can't shake this feeling like i --
感觉我并不属于这里  你懂我的意思吗
Like i don't belong here, you know what i mean?
我应该做点别的事情  而不是做一个客服
Like i should do something more than sit in a cubicle.
我想大多数做客服的人
I think most people who work in
都是这么想的
a cubicle feel  own last name
不  不光这个
No. well,look, it's more than that.
比如  我不喜欢我的工作
Like -- like i don't like my job.
我不喜欢这个小镇  我不喜欢我的着装
I don't like this town. i don't like my clothes.
我不喜欢自己的姓
I don't like my own last name.
我不知道要怎么解释
I -- i don't know how else to explain it,
除非
Except that...
就是感觉我应该做点别的事情
It feels like i should be doing something else.
我骨子里有些
There's just... something in my blood.
好像我生来就些别的什么事
Like i was destined for something different.
你呢
What about you?
有没有同感
You ever feel that way?
我不信命运
I don't believe in destiny.
我不相信
I do believe in dealing with
摆在我们面前的事情
What's right in front of us, though.
好吧 我们现在干吗
All right. so,what do we do now?
做我们擅长的  小萨姆
We do what i do best, Sammy.
研究先
Research.
好吧
Okay.
你刚才叫我  小萨姆
Did you just call me "Sammy"?
我叫了吗
Did i?
我想是的
I think you did.
你叫了
Yeah.
别
Don't.
抱歉
Sorry.
中头彩了
Oh,jackpot!
你找到什么了
What you got?
我找到了世上最好的网页
I just found the best site ever.
现实中的猎鬼者
Real, actual ghost hunters.
这些人是天才  先看看
These guys are genius. check it out.
教学视频吗
Instructional videos?
我们知道你观看的原因
We know why you're watching.
你遇到了麻烦
You've got a problem.
事关鬼魂
A ghost problem.
恶鬼缠身
A ghost-related problem.
鬼魂  类似鬼魂
A-a ghost -- it's like a ghost-adjacent --
一个关乎鬼魂的问题
It's like a problem, and the ghost --
随便吧
Whatever.
你算来对地方了
Well,you've come to the right place.
独一无二的好地方
The only decent place, really,
因为抓鬼特工队知道解决之道
Because the ghostfacers know how to solve it.
就是这样
Period.
仔细看  认真学
Watch and learn.
看好了  跨入超自然之战的第一步
See,the first step in any supernatural fight...
弄清你在对付的对象
Figure out what you're up against.
是他  那个鬼魂
That's him. that's the ghost.
P.t.桑多弗  死于1916年
P.t. sandover -- died 1916.
毕生为其事业而奋斗
Devoted his life to his work.
无妻无子
No wife,no kids.
曾说他就是公司
Used to say he was the company
整栋楼充斥着他的血脉
And his very blood pumped through the building.
靠  是个工作狂
Wow. okay. so,slight workaholic.
或许他还在那里
Maybe he's still here,
看管着公司
You know,watching over the company --
甚至为了它杀人
Even killing for it.
还有  看起来这不是他第一次杀人
Plus,turns out this isn't the first time
大楼里的人开始自杀
People started killing themselves in the building.
1929年 大萧条
1929 -- the crash.
是啊  很多人从高楼跳下
Yeah,but lots of guys jumped off
共有17人自杀
of lots of high-es had 17 suicid
哪家公司会有17人自杀呢
How many companies had 17 suicides?
好吧  P.T.桑多弗  公司的守护者
Okay,so,p.t. sandover -- protector of the company.
他灵魂苏醒  开始采取行动
His ghost wakes up and becomes active
经济不景气时
During times of grave economic distress.
继人们所谈论的大萧条后
Well,i mean,the worst time we've
又一次危机
seen since the great depression to talk about it
就是指现在了
Is now.
是啊  形势不大好
Yeah,now sucks.
我的投资正在缩水
My portfolio's in the sewer.
我都不愿提
I don't even want to talk about it.
所以呢  桑多弗  仍在坚持底线
So, Sandover's helping the bottom line...
通过干掉一些典型员工
By zapping some model employees.
是啊  我是指  伊恩和保罗
Yeah. i mean, Hian and paul --
貌似他要把他们变成另一种人
It was like he turned them into different people.
勤劳努力的工蜂  正是这样
Perfect worker bees -- exactly.
以此来效忠公司
So devoted to the company
不成功便成仁
That they would commit hara-kiri if they failed it.
更有趣的是
One more interesting fact --
大楼以前没那么高
The building wasn't always that high.
只有14层
Used to be 14 floors.
鬼魂袭击的房间号是1444
And the room where the ghost attacked,1444 --
很久以前  曾是那老头子的办公室
Once upon a time, that was the old man's office.
一看到它
Once you've got that thing in your sights...
就杀了它
You kill it!
用特制的猎鬼武器
Using special ghost-hunting weapons.
首先呢  盐
First,salt.
对鬼魂来说如同强酸
It's like acid to ghosts.
浓硫酸
Burny acid.
可不是摇头丸
Not lsd.
不对  是鬼魂的灾难之旅
No. it's a bad trip for ghosts.
接下来  铁
Next up -- iron.
所以说扳手会有用
That's why the wrench worked.
用尽全力  在一瞬间打散游魂
Pure power in your hand -- dissipates ghosts instantly.
接下来的小技巧
Next little trick --
是我们从没用的白痴那里学来的
We learned this from those useless douche bags...
我们讨厌的
That we hate...
温切斯特家族
...the winchesters.
-枪  -霰弹枪弹壳
- Gun. - shotgun shell.
用盐粒塞满
Pack it up with fresh rock salt.
非常有效
Very effective.
相当有效
V-very effective.
不过温切斯特家族依旧很烂
Winchesters still suck ass,though.
的确
Affirmative.
最主要的是烂
Suckage -- major.
我们要从哪里弄枪
Where do we even get a gun?
枪械店吗
Gun store?
从那里弄需要一定时间申请
Isn't there,like,some kind of waiting period or something?
-我想也是  -那怎么办
- I think so. - then how in the hell?
我不知道  看起来很不可思议
I don't know,man. it seems pretty impossible,honestly.
是啊
Right.
刚提到的超级烦人的
The aforementioned super-annoying
温切斯特白痴
Winchester douche-nozzles
还教了些别的
Also taught us this one other thing.
你们得火烧遗骸
You have to burn the remains.
好吧  接下来的部分有些恶心
Okay,this next part gets a little gross.
有时候  你得掘尸
Sometimes...you might have to...dig up the body.
-抱歉  -在某些州不合法
- Sorry. - it's illegal in some states.
所有州
All states.
可能所有州
Possibly all states.
桑多弗被火化了
Sandover was cremated.
什么
What?
那我们该怎么做
So, what do we do now?
如果遗体已被火化
Now,if the deceased has been cremated...
-别慌  -别急
- Don't panic. - don't panic.
找找是否有其他遗物
You just got to look for some other remains.
盒子里的头发  也可能是指甲  乳牙
Hair in a locket,maybe, fingernails,baby teeth --
乳牙
Milk teeth.
遗传物质  知道我们在说什么吧
Genetic material. you know what we're talking about.
找到它
Go find it.
好好战斗吧  新手们
Fight well, young lions.
祝福你
Godspeed.
把你手机调到对讲模式
Set your cellphone to walkie-talkie
以防我们被分散
In case we get separated.
我们怎么可能在一栋摩天大楼里
How the hell are we gonna find some ancient speck of dna
找到八百年前的DNA呢
In a skyscraper?
那灵异的储藏室
Well,that creepy storeroom used
以前是桑多弗的办公室吧
to be sandover's office,right?
你在这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
没什么  我只是
Uh...nothing. i just --
跟我走
Come with me.
伙计  听我说  我是在这里工作的
Man,l-listen -- it's okay. I-I work here.
别和我说  和警察说去吧
Whatever. tell it to the cops.
来吧
Well,come on.
什么
What?
上次发生这种情况
Last time this happened,
他们花了两小时才找到这里
It took them two hours to get here.
那就等着吧
Let's just wait.
说真的  我还是等着好了
Seriously -- i'll wait.
听着  我不想把时间浪费在这里
Look,i don't have the rest of my life here.
你没事吧
Hey. you okay?
等会再打给你
Call you back.
迪恩  你在吗
Dean, are you there
在  我想我找到了
Yeah. listen,i think i got it.
到22楼来找我
Meet me on 22.
好的
Okay. yeah.
不过  我要爬楼梯
Just,uh... take the stairs.
好多血
That's a lot of blood.
我知道
Yeah,i know.
好吧
Right.
就在这里
So,uh,in there.
P.t.桑多弗的手套
P.t. Sandover's gloves.
对
Yeah.
要不要打个赌
How much you want to bet there's
看看里面是否有一点DNA
a little smidge DNA in there
比如剪下来的一小片指甲
You know,like a fingernail clipping
或者头发什么的
or a hair something
你准备好了吗
So,you ready?
不知道
I have no idea.
我也不知道
Me neither.
拿出来吧
Go for it.
好吧
Right.
干的漂亮
Nice!
迪恩
Dean!
接得漂亮
Nice catch.
是吗
Right?
太牛逼了
That was amazing!
是吗
Right?
哥们  我得说
Man,I got to tell you, I've never
我从没做过这么有意思的事
had so much fun doing in my life.
我也没有
Me neither.
这也是个锻炼啊  是不
It was a hell of a workout, too,wasn't it?
我们应该继续干这事
We should keep doing this.
我知道
I know.
我说真的
I mean it.
外面一定还有其他的鬼
There got to be other ghosts out there.
我们可以帮助更多的人
We could help a lot of people.
没错  就像抓鬼特工队那样
Yeah,right. we'd be like the ghostfacers.
不  来真的
No,really.
我是说要来真的
I mean...for real.
什么
What?
辞职踏上捉鬼之路吗
Quit our jobs and hit the road?
对啊
Exactly.
我们靠什么生存
How would we live?
你搞笑呢
You got to be kidding me.
难道我们通过盗用信用卡过活吗
How would we get by -- with stolen credit cards? huh?
每晚都吃着那些高脂肪的垃圾食品
Eating diner food drenched in saturated fats?
两个人每晚都挤在一个汽车旅馆的房间里休息
Sharing a crap motel room every night?
-那些都只是细枝末节罢了  -事无巨细  都不能忽视
- That's all just details. - details are everything!
你不可能带着一腔热血就开始和鬼灵对抗吧
You don't want to go fighting ghosts without any hearts
好吧  我还是坦白吧
All right. uh...confession.
坦白啥
What?
还记得我跟你提到过的那些
Remember those dreams I told you about,
关于鬼怪的梦
With the ghosts?
当然  怎么了
Yeah.
梦里我同他们战斗
I was fighting them.
然后呢
Okay.
跟你一起
With you.
我们  在梦里  应该就是
We were... these, like...
猎鬼者
Hunters.
咱俩还是朋友
And we were friends.
确切地说  就像是两兄弟
More like brothers, really.
我是想说  如果那一切是真的
I mean, what if that's who we really are?
你想想看我们都在同一个地方  又在一起工作
I mean, you saw us back there, working together.
而鬼怪有能力搅乱人的思维
T-the ghost was scrambling people's brains.
说不定也搅乱了我们俩的
What if it scrambled ours?
确实疯了
That's insane.
是吗
Is it?
稍微想像一下
Think about it for just one second.
若是这一切是我们假想中的生活
What if we think this is our life...
其实并不是真的呢
But it's not?
行了  伙计  那个鬼已经灭了  我们还好好地活着呢
Hey, man, the ghost is dead,  and we're still standing.
抱歉这么直白  但
I mean, I'm sorry, but --
听着  就我所知  这绝对不是我们真正的身份
Look, all I know is, this isn't who we're supposed to be.
不
No.
我确实是迪恩·斯密斯  清楚吗  是市场销售部主管
I'm Dean Smith, okay? director of sales and marketing.
毕业于斯坦福大学
I went to Stanford.
我父亲叫鲍勃  而我母亲
My father's name is Bob, my mother's name
名叫埃伦  我还有个妹妹  叫乔
is Ellen, and my sis name Jo,
你最后一次和他们聊天是什么时候
When's the last time you talked to them?
和他们中的任何一个
To any of them?
行了  你不过是对生活感到沮丧  所以才将梦和现实混淆了
Okay. you're upset. you're upset, you're confused --
是的  因为我孤身搬来这个城市
Yeah, 'cause I only moved here
因为我刚刚和我的未婚妻麦迪森分手
'cause I just broke up with my fiancee, Madison.
但是我打电话给她  电话那头竟是个该死的动物医院
But I called her number and I got a damn animal hospital.
好了  你到底在说些什么啊
Okay, what are you saying?
你是想说  我的家人根本就是虚构的
Y-you trying to say that -- that my family isn't real?
我们的记忆全是捏造出来的
That we've been injected with fake memories?
拜托
Come on!
我只知道  我会有这种想法都是出于我的本能
All I know is, I got this feeling in my gut.
而我知道  我知道  那是发自内心深处的
And I know -- I know that, deep down,
你一定也有这种感觉
You got to be feeling it, too.
我们肯定有其他身份
We're supposed to be something else.
你绝不会就是个酒囊饭袋的小白领
You're not just some corporate douche bag.
那不是你
This isn't you.
我了解你
I know you.
了解我
Know me?
你不了解我  伙计
You don't know me, pal.
你该走了
You should go.
我不干了
I quit.
有空吗
Got a minute?
有  当然有
Sure. of course.
感觉怎么样  迪恩
How are you feeling, Dean?
挺好的
Uh...great.
你似乎有点儿疲惫
You look a little tired.
做事太拼了吧  我猜
Been working hard, i gather.
别谦虚了  我都听说了
Ah, don't be modest. I hear everything.
而且非常满意
And I'm pleased with what i'm hearing.
所以我此行的重要目的就是让你也高兴一下
That's why it's important to me that you're happy.
这个数目的奖金满意吗
How's that for a bonus?
真够大笔的
Very generous.
纯粹是一己私欲
Purely selfish.
就是希望能把你牢牢绑住
I want to make sure you're not going anywhere.
你说真的
Are you sure?
当然
Positive.
你可是桑多弗梦寐以求的人才啊  孩子
You are sandover material, son
有抱负  并且清楚未来之路该如何走
Real go-getter, carving your own way.
谢谢你的赞扬  我定努力
Well, thanks. I try.
我可以预见你将来必成大器
I see big things in your future.
更甚至于
Maybe even...
可以成为东五大湖区分部的高级副总裁
Senior v.p., eastern great lakes division.
我不会看走眼的  你一定办得到
Don't get me wrong. you'll have to work for it
虽然全年无休  餐无定时
Seven days a week, lunch at your desk
但不出十年半载的  你必定会有出头之日
But in 8 to 10 short years, that could be you.
承蒙您看得起
Uh, well, thank you.
谢谢你  老板
Thank you, sir.
只是
It's,um...
只不过
But...
我想正式提出辞呈
I am giving my notice.
你在开玩笑吧
This is a joke.
你逗我玩的吧  对不
You're kidding me, right?
不  我
No, I...
我最近  应该说就在刚才
I recently, uh, very recently
突然意识到了还有更重要的事等着我去做
Realized that I have some other work I have to do.
那对我而言可以说是举足轻重
It's, uh... very important to me.
其他工作  跳槽吗
Other work? another company?
不是  我  很难解释
No, I -- it's hard to explain.
其实是
It's just that this...
这  其实就是
This is, it's just...
我的人生不该如此
...it's not who I'm supposed to be.
笑什么
What?
迪恩  迪恩  迪恩
Dean, Dean, Dean.
最终
Finally.
该死的这究竟是
What the hell?
我干嘛打领带
Why am I wearing a tie?
老天  我饿得肝肠寸断了
My god, am i hungry.
欢迎回来
Welcome back.
慢着  我是不是
Wait. did I
我刚才是不是被点化了
Did i just get touched by
你是天使  对不
You're an angel, aren't you?
我是撒迦利亚(施洗者约翰之父)
I'm Zachariah.
太好了  真是没完没了  又来一个
Oh, great. that's all I need, is another one of you guys.
我可不是什么又一个  迪恩  我是卡西迪奥的上司
I'm hardly "another one," Dean. I'm Castiel's superior.
相信我  我根本就没兴趣降尘来此
Believe me, I had no interest in popping down here
更别说  还要附身于这恶心的躯壳里
And into one of these smelly things.
但在发生了尤利尔那件憾事之后
But after the unfortunate... situation with Uriel,
我想我必须亲自走一趟
I felt it necessary to pay a visit
以确保所有人仍各司其职
Get my ducks in a row.
我可不是你的玩物
I am not one of your ducks.
注意下你的态度
Starting with your attitude.
这是干嘛  搞这么多事就是想给我个当头棒喝吗
Oh, so, what? this, this was all some sort of a lesson?
而这就是你想告诉我的
Is that what you're telling me?
真有创意
Well, very creative.
那你应该再看看我的其他剪辑
You should see my decoupage.
我汗毛都竖起来了
Gross.
不用了  谢谢你的邀请
No, thank you.
那是怎么回事  我刚刚经历的都是幻觉吗
So,what, I'm... I'm just hallucinating all this?
是吗
Is that it?
不全是  实地  实事
Not at all. real place, real haunting.
唯一费了点儿神的就是
Just plunked you in the middle
改造了下你的记忆
Without the benefit of your memories.
就是为了动摇我  是吗
Just to shake things up? hmm?
你们这些家伙就这么喜欢看着我们
So you guys can have fun watching us run around
穿着猴子装像个小丑似的东奔西跑
Like ass-clowns in -- in monkey suits?
这只是为了让你正视
To prove to you that the path
你内心真正的自我
you're on is trul
你就是个猎鬼者
You're a hunter.
而非你父亲造就了你
Not because your dad made you.
更非上帝给你赎罪的机会
Not because god called you back from hell.
而是因为你的本性就是如此
But because it is what you are.
而且你也喜欢这行
And you love it.
每次在你面对黑暗时  你总有法子自寻光明
You'll find your way to it in the dark every single time,
如果没有这一切  你就会觉得生活苦不堪言
And you're miserable without it.
迪恩  面对现实吧  你应该是乐于此道的
Dean, Let's be real here -- you're good at this.
你能成功的  你将阻止一切
You'll be successful. you will stop it.
阻止什么
Stop what?
天启吗  路西法吗
The apocalypse, huh? Lucifer?
到底是什么  说明白点儿  伙计
What? be specific, man!
命运赋予你的使命  你是无法抗拒的
You'll do everything you're destined to do.
毫无可能
All of it.
但我了解  了解
But I know, I know.
你觉得自己不够强大  所以退却了
You're not strong enough. you're scared.
而你父亲的事  更让你无法释怀  是吗
You got daddy issues. you can't do it, right?
管你是不是天使  我都要赏你一拳
Angel or not, I will stab you in your face.
我刚刚所说的一切
All I'm saying is...
正是你内心真正的想法
It's how you look at it.
大多数的人在面对生死抉择的那一刻时根本无能为力
Most folks live and die without moving anything more
所以他们只能长眠地下
Than the dirt it takes to bury them.
但你却会去努力扭转
You get to change things...
挽救他们
Save people.
甚至挽救整个世界
Maybe even the world.
一直以来  你都开着那辆经典型车
All the while, you drive a classic car
一路寻花问柳地泡MM
And fornicate with women.
其实那不是亵渎  而是一种恩赐
This isn't a curse -- it's a gift.
看在上帝的份上  迪恩  别在自怨自艾了
So, for god's sakes, Dean, quit whining about it.
看看周遭
Look around.
命运比你悲惨的人多得去了
There are plenty of fates worse than yours.
懂我的意思了吗
So, you with me?
要不要立马去泡杯拿铁给自己果果腹啊
You want to go steam yourself another latte?
或许你已经准备好重新振作
Or are you ready to stand up...
做回自己呢
...and be who you really are?